easybizchina.com 2009-04-05

# EasyBizChina - China Manufacturers, Suppliers, China Trade, Exporter, Importer, B2B Marketplace

|  | 

|     
---  
|    
---  
This Privacy Policy sets forth the policy of EasyBizChina.com ("EasyBizChina") with respect to the privacy of the persons (the "Users") who use the web site at EasyBizChina.com (this "Site"). Because EasyBizChina gathers certain types of information about the Users of this Site, we believe you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the use of the information we collect. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we gather, how we use it, what steps we take to maintain security and confidentiality, and how to correct or change erroneous or outdated information. By using this Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy set out below.  
1\. Information we compile   
In general, we gather information about all users collectively, such as what areas users visit most frequently and what services users access the most. This information, which is automatically retrieved, lets EasyBizChina analyze site traffic and service offerings as well as and manage its relationships with Users of this Site.   
When registering with us, we will request various levels of information, including your name, address, phone/fax number, e-mail address and other business information. This information enables us to ascertain the appropriate level of access to site (Viewer, Buyer, Supplier or all) for each user. This information also better enables us to provide you with content relevant to your interests and provides us with aggregate demographic data that EasyBizChina uses to improve the service offered to Users.   
In addition to registration, EasyBizChina may, from time to time, request personal information, such as when we solicit feedback from Users with respect to the use of parts of all of the Site and our services.   
   
|  2\. What does EasyBizChina do with the information it collects?  
---  
EasyBizChina may use customer contact information from the registration form to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which EasyBizChina.com determines that you might be interested. EasyBizChina may use personal information to determine the demographics of our Users and to distribute statistics and general marketplace information. These demographics will always represent aggregate information and will never identify a specific user.  
   
All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on the Site and therefore accessible by any internet user. Any Publishing Information that you disclose to EasyBizChina.com becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information. You should exercise caution when deciding to include personal or proprietary information in the Publishing Information that you submit to our Site.  
   
Certain other non-personal information of visitors is also recorded by the standard operation of EasyBizChina's Internet servers. This information is primarily used to provide visitors to EasyBizChina.com with an enhanced online experience. Information tracked includes, but is not limited to, the type of browser being used by the visitor, the type of operating system, and the domain name of the visitor's Internet service provider. EasyBizChina may disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe the service to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. Aggregated data does not include personal information such as an individual's name, phone number, or email address.  
   
Also, please be aware that advertisers or Web sites that are linked to EasyBizChina.com may collect personally identifiable information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to EasyBizChina.com.  
   
EasyBizChina contains links to other sites. EasyBizChina is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. EasyBizChina makes or has future plans to make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available on the Site. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  
   
EasyBizChina may also use your personal information to (i) resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; and (ii) prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and enforce the Terms and Conditions of our website and our Privacy Policy.  
   
|  3.Disclosure of Information   
---  
We reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of EasyBizChina.com, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.   
We also reserve the right to disclose Collected Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.  
If we have reason to believe that a User is in breach of the Terms of User Agreement or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to EasyBizChina or others.   
   
EasyBizChina may also disclose customer personal information to (i) service providers who help with business operation, (ii) EasyBizChina's affiliates, and (iii) other business entities in the event that EasyBizChina plans to merge with or be acquired by such business entity.   
   
|  4\. Cookies  
---  
We use "cookies" to store specific information about you and track your visits to our Site. A "cookies" is a small data file that some Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that a Web site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.  
   
If you do not de-activate or erase the cookie, each time you use the same computer to access our Site, our web servers will be notified of your visit to our Site and in turn we may have knowledge of your visit and the pattern of your usage. Generally, we use cookies to identify you and enable us to access your Registration Information, so you do not have to re-enter it; gather statistical information about usage by Users; research visiting patters and help target advertisements based on User interests; assist our partners to track User visits to the Site and process orders; and track progress and participation in promotions.  
   
You can determine if and how a cookie will be accepted by configuring your browser's which is installed in the computer you are using to access the Site. If you desire, you can change those configurations in your browser. By setting your preferences in the browser, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is sent, or you can reject all cookies. If you reject all cookies by choosing the cookie-disabling function in your browser, you may be required to re-enter your information on our Site more often and certain features of our Site may be unavailable.   
   
|  5\. User Options -- Opt-In/Opt Out  
---  
If for any reason EasyBizChina does decide to collect and use personally identifiable information for any purpose not listed above, EasyBizChina will inform users about its use of personally identifiable information. Reasons for collecting personal information could include billing, provision of customer service, network management, customer surveys, subscriptions, provision of offers of related services and other exchanges of information at its Website.  
   
As mentioned above, EasyBizChina may use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. EasyBizChina communications will solicit Opt-in/Opt-out responses for future communications.   
   
The opt-in means users agree to receive message through a confirmation message from EasyBizChina. The opt-out means users can leave or unsubscribe from the list at any time and not receive further mailings.   
   
|  6.Security   
---  
The integrity and the security of information pertaining to our Users is extremely important to EasyBizChina. We use our best efforts to use this information only to further the commercial objectives of the Users for which this Site was designed. All of your personal information is stored on our servers at a location designed specifically to ensure that no unauthorized individuals have access to the server or its data. Through the natural course of commercial activity facilitated by this Site industry professionals will access information that is covered by this Privacy Policy and may have retained a copy of your postings in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of information in these instances.   
   
Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.   
   
No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.   
   
|  7\. EasyBizChina Privacy Policy Changes  
---  
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy for EasyBizChina, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. By using the EasyBizChina.com services, you signify your assent to the EasyBizChina.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site or the services. Your continued use of EasyBizChina.com or the services following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.   
   
EasyBizChina.com welcomes your continuous input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you. You may send us your comments and responses to   
service@easybizchina.com.
